MARSHALL LANNERS

WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer and software engineer with 6+ years of customer service, and 2 years office management experience. Excellent team player, reliable, trustworthy, and curious individual always seeking ways to learn new technologies. Solid understanding of HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Node, Python, and C.

PROJECTS

Let's Get Tacos

HTML | React | Node | Redux | CSS | Firebase | Heroku

Developed on a team of 4, built in 5 weeks, integrated Api, contributed to React, Node backend, and UI for application.

Application interacts with the Yelp and Google Maps Api to schedule events for users to meetup and eat tacos together.

Github: https://github.com/Lambda-School-

Labs/labs10-taco-run

Website: https://taco-run-c453f.firebaseapp.com/

Spotty

HTML | React | CSS | Firebase | Heroku Individual project

Application uses the Spotify Api for users to interact listen to music and post music tracks to their Spotify account.

Github: https://github.com/lanners-marshall/spotty Website: https://react-spotty.herokuapp.com/

EDUCATION

Lambda School · Sept. 2018 to Mar. 2019 Certificate Full Stack Web Development and Computer Science

California Polytechnic University · May 2007 to Jan. 2010 Bachelor of Science Business Administration, Management

CONTACT

 \searrow

in mlanners/

lanners-marshall

lanners.marshall@gmail.com

mlanners.com

**** 206-475-7021

♀ Seattle, Wa

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, REACT, NODE, JAVASCRIPT, PYTHON, C, FIREBASE, HEROKU, NETLIFY

EMPLOYMENT

Lambda School

Remote

WEB PT 9 Team Leader · July 2019 to Current Team Leader for Lambda School part time full stack web development. Mentors students in full stack web development along with handling student attendance and progress, conducting standup meetings, and grading assignments.

Ricoh @ Amazon

Seattle

Senior on Site Service Associate ·

July 2016 to Nov. 2018

Operated high volume business to meet all their shipping needs of Amazon employees, utilized high volume duplicating equipment, performed associated copying tasks, provided copier maintenance and repair of customer site equipment, and also conducted business deliveries.

- Winner of BSC of the Quarter in addition to 2 customer service awards.

VOLUNTEERING

Code Fellows ·

Teachers Assistant - Night Course - Ruby on Rails

Seattle

Troubleshooted problems with students
Helped Grade Homework
Assisted students in the understanding of Ruby and
Ruby on Rails